All right, so as I mentioned before, one of the
most important things in this GNOME desktop interface is the terminal.
So let's go start the terminal
by typing term and pressing Enter.
Now, the font size is a little bit small, so
I'm using Ctrl Shift plus to increase it a little bit.
And there we can
see this should be readable.
Oh, and I just clicked the title bar
to fill the entire screen with this application.
Now, within the terminal
there is terminal preferences.
And these terminal
preferences might be interesting.
In the profiles I can
see my untitled profile, and in
this profile I can define
how I want it to behave.
And as you can see, lots of
options are available within these terminal preferences.
And for the rest of it,
well, it's a terminal. And what do
we do in a terminal? We
type commands like Echo hello world.
And there you
can see it works.